let MCQS = [{
     question: "Below are examples of communication situations EXCEPT?",
    choice1: "Feedback",
    choice2: "Decoding",
    choice3: "Encoding",
    choice4: "Communication",
    answer: 1
},
            {
            question: "It  refers to the way or mode the message flows or is transmitted through. ",
    choice1: "Message",
    choice2: "Noise",
    choice3: "Channel",
    choice4: "Feedback",
    answer: 2
},
            {
           question: "It can help senders know if their message was received and understood.",
    choice1: "Noise",
    choice2: "Feedback",
    choice3: "Clarity",
    choice4: "Channel",
    answer: 1
},
            {
            question: "This model also called Schramm Model.",
    choice1: "Interactive Model",
    choice2: "Transactional Model",
    choice3: "Model of Communication",
    choice4: "Linear Model",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "Who original developed Linear Model of communication?",
    choice1: "Wilbur Schramm",
    choice2: "Shannon and Weaver",
    choice3: "Dean Barnlund",
    choice4: "Frank Dance",
    answer: 1
},
            {
            question: "Below are examples of Transactional Model of communication EXCEPT?",
    choice1: "Telephone Call",
    choice2: "Skype Call",
    choice3: "Broadcasting",
    choice4: "Interactive Training",
    answer: 2
},
            {
               question: "It is a two way process and the sender received a feedback from the receiver.",
    choice1: "Linear Model ",
    choice2: "Transactional Model ",
    choice3: "Decoder ",
    choice4: "Interactive Model ",
    answer: 3
},{
               question: "The transmitter which converts the message into signals.",
    choice1: "Linear Model",
    choice2: "Interactive Model",
    choice3: "Encoder",
    choice4: "Decoder",
    answer: 2
},
            {
               question: "Check your tone of voice, pronunciation, and speech rate.",
    choice1: "Keep Focused",
    choice2: "Minimize Distraction",
    choice3: "Speak Intelligibly",
    choice4: "Be Specific",
    answer: 2
},
            {
               question: "Function to motivate or to inspire someone by your speech or advice.",
    choice1: "Motivation",
    choice2: "Regulation or Control",
    choice3: "Emotional Expression",
    choice4: "Information Dissemination",
    answer: 0
},
            {
               question: "Use simple and not confusing words to your audience.",
    choice1: "Speak Intelligibly",
    choice2: "Minimize Distraction",
    choice3: "Be Specific",
    choice4: "Listen with your Eyes and Ears",
    answer: 2
},           
			{
            question: "You should listen what people say and act.",
    choice1: "Speak Intelligibly",
    choice2: "Minimize Distraction",
    choice3: "Listen with your Eyes and Ears",
    choice4: "Do not Jump to Conclusion",
    answer: 2
},
            {
               question: "You must based on facts, evidences, and reliable information.",
    choice1: "Do not Jump to Conclusion",
    choice2: "Listen with your Eyes and Ears",
    choice3: "Keep Focused",
    choice4: "Minimize Distraction",
    answer: 3
}, 
            {
            question: "You should state your purpose of communication.",
    choice1: "Intrapersonal Communication",
    choice2: "Interpersonal Communication",
    choice3: "Public Communication",
    choice4: "Mass Communication",
    answer: 1
},
            {
            question: "It pertains to use suitable words to deliver message or speech.",
    choice1: "Brevity",
    choice2: "Ethics",
    choice3: "Appropriateness",
    choice4: "Vividness",
    answer: 2
}];